davidwygant.com 2013-04-23

# David Wygant - The Dating Expert that men and women trust most with their love lives

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc.'s Statement of Privacy

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. are committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to davidwygant.com and governs data collection and usage at all David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. 

Please read the David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. Statement of Privacy. davidwygant.com is a general audience website, intended for users 18 years of age and older. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.

**Information We Gather Automatically**

When you visit this site, certain non-personally identifying information is recorded automatically by the standard operation of our Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your computer’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number that your Internet service provider assigns to your computer whenever you surf the Internet) is gathered in order to facilitate our online operations and to assure an efficient online experience for you. We may also use or share this information for security purposes, to generate group statistics about our user community, or as required by law.

We may use your IP address or other automatically recorded information, in cooperation with your Internet provider, to identify you if it is necessary to contact you or to bring legal action against you because you are violating the Terms and Conditions of use for this site or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company’s rights or property, other users of this site or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

We allow third-party companies, including AddThis, to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

As an E-commerce website, davidwygant.com collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by davidwygant.com is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases, and for sending messages and correspondence via email. 

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. do not collect any information about your computer hardware and software. David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from davidwygant.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. 

We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the davidwygant.com website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. and their operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested. It is possible that David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from davidwygant.com and to send you requested information including, but not limited to, newsletters and emails about davidwygant.com. David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. do not sell, rent or lease their customer lists to third parties. David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. do not collect, use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations.

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on davidwygant.com; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc., including their Websites; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of davidwygant.com or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. or their affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. abide by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Control of Your Personal Information**

davidwygant.com offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences by emailing support at davidwygant.com. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records.

You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from davidwygant.com by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we use a secure payment gateway so your information is protected.

**Copyright Information**

**** Some images on davidwygant.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)

**Claims of Infringement**

**** If you believe that any content appearing on davidwygant.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know. E-Mail support@davidwygant.com with following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf

Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.

**Changes to this Statement**

David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how davidwygant.com will use your personal information, David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc.will use your personal information, davidwygant.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. David Wygant, DW Productions, Wygant Creative Group and Wygant Productions, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how davidwygant.com is protecting your information.
